for one year of my life I was a
kindergarten teacher like you you just
think you have I was just in over my
head some of you parents know you have a
kid that shouldn't have been going to
school at 6 years
old they weren't house broken yet you
know that you know that you know which
ones you are you'd send your kids to
school with an extra set of
clothes that's rude don't do that that's
rude cuz that's a mindset you look at
your kid you're like there is no way
this kid goes 6 hours same pants that is
not going to
happen never happened so
far and there's also no way I'm going
over there to change those pants that's
not going to happen either let's let
that 22-year-old with $40,000 in student
loan debt and questioning his life let's
let him do
that let's break his Spirit day one
let's show him what reality is
like cuz I didn't know I was going to
have to do that change kids pee pants I
didn't know first day of school just
stand there this kid comes up and goes
like I peed in my pants and I was like
that ain't going to get your girls bro
you're going to want to work on that
that your game is
weak if I were you I'd go lay on that
bean bag chair back there it's absorb it
you'll absorb it all
just 5 minutes on the front rotate 5
minutes on the
back you're probably
good then it dawned on me I got to go
change his kid's pants I've never done
that I've never changed a kids pants
before I walk in the bathroom I'm like
don't tell anybody about this I don't
know that may have been harsh that's
maybe not what I want to say right now
um I don't want that getting echoed dear
parents we went to the bathroom you told
me not to say anything about it
no not needs context tell everybody you
know what don't tell I don't know what
to do I just want you to forget about
this even
happening so we go in there and I'm like
Jal protocol bro you stare at the wall I
stare at that wall we don't make eye
contact that's what we're doing right
now I want you to lock in on that tile
like a fighter
pilot no side eye either way weirdo
we're not doing that
[Music]
game grab like the side of his sweats
like pulling them down and as soon as
they get like mid thigh level this
monster throws his hands above his head
and it starts leaning in like there we
go yeah swinging what are you doing
Magic Mike are you kidding me right
now to go burn my eyes out of my head
it's
ridiculous